lastbit.com 2004-12-04

# Lastbit Software Products - password recovery, security software and utilities

**Short Version**  
We keep all your personal information secret. We don't share it with anyone else. 

Anything you post on this site or send to the company in connection with this site or our product shall be deemed sole and exclusive property of the company. 

**Long Version**  
This document sets forth the LastBit Software Privacy Policy for this Web site www.lastbit.com (The Site). The team at www.lastbit.com wants to treat your personal information with the respect, which it deserves, as well as treating it in accordance with the law.  
The following statement discloses the personal information (personal information is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify and contact person to whom such information pertains) gathering and dissemination practices for this Site. 

Anything you post on this site or send to the company in connection with this site or our product shall be deemed sole and exclusive property of the company. 

**Changing in Privacy Policy**  
All personal information that we collect and maintain will be the subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in the effect at the time of such collection. LastBit Software reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion and will provide notice on the home page of the Site. 

**Collecting of personal information**  
As a visitor of the site you can engage many activities (like downloading demo version) without providing any personal information. When personal information is required (for example for subscribing to the newsletter) we clearly state what information is required and why. We never use collected information for purposes other then mentioned above, in particular we never send unsolicited emails.   
When you use the Site LastBit Software may also collect certain technical and routing information, we may log your IP address to facilitate diagnosing problems with our server and to administer our web site. This information is primarily used for general traffic tracking and security. 

**How personal information is used**  
When you place an order with us, we collect contact information (like your email address). Contact information is used only to get in touch with you when necessary, i.e. sending you the product(s) you ordered and contacting you if there's a problem with your order. LastBit Software may collect information about the use of the Site; such as how many users visit us daily. This information is collected without identifying any user individually. LastBit Software may use this non-identifying data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.

**Your choices with respect to personal information.**  
LastBit Software recognizes the importance of responsibility for the use of information collected on this Site. Without your consent, LastBit Software will not communicate any information regarding products and special offers available from LastBit Software to you. Except in the particular circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, LastBit software will also not provide your name and e-mail address to other companies or organizations. LastBit Software may provide your personal information if necessary in order to protect the rights of LastBit Software. 

**Protection your personal information**  
Personal information that you provide in connection with ordering LastBit Software product resides on a secure server and is only accessible to selected LastBit software personnel via password. This site does not store credit card numbers for processed orders. We are taking appropriate steps to make impossible unauthorized access or disclosure of the information you share with us. 

**Use of Cookies**  
Our Site uses cookies to track information about our visitors. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a WEB server and can only be read by the server that gives it to you. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

**Privacy-related feedback**  
You opinion on our privacy policy is important to us. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy or the practices contact us.
